flipagram.com 2013-12-20

# Flipagram - Bring Moments to Life! Create short video stories from your photos, set to music you love!

Cheerful, Inc. (“Cheerful”) is committed to protecting your privacy online and provides this Privacy Policy to inform our website and app visitors and users of our services of policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personally identifiable information received from users of the Cheerful Websites and Services. For purposes of this Agreement, "Websites" refers to all Cheerful sites ([www.chee.rs](http://www.chee.rs/ "Cheers"), [www.Cheerfulinc.com](http://www.cheerfulinc.com/ "Cheerful Inc."), [www.flipagr.am](http://flipagram.com/ "Flipagram"), [www.flipabackground.com](http://www.flipabackground.com/ "Flipabackground"), [www.gri.pe](http://www.gri.pe/ "Gripe")) and "Services" includes but not limited to the Cheerful mobile applications (Cheers, Flipagram, Flipabackground and Gripe) along with any other Cheerful services in which users can create/submit content and interact with posted content as well as other registered users. The terms "we," "us," and "our" refer to Cheerful, Inc. "You" refers to you, as a user of the Website or the Services. By accepting our Privacy Policy and Terms of Service (found here: Terms of Service) you consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Policy applies to all site visitors, registered users, and all other users of the Services. 

## Website Visitors

Like most website and app operators, Cheerful collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Cheerful’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Cheerful visitors use its Website. From time to time, Cheerful may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its Website.

## Information Collection and Use

Our primary goal in collecting Personal Information is to provide you with a personalized, useful, and efficient experience. We collect the following types of information from our users:

**Personal Information.** If you create an account, we ask for and record Personal Information such as your email address. Your Personal Information will not be visible to other users. Cheerful may contact you using the Personal Information you provided to communicate with you and to send you information that are aligned with our Services for which you signed-up for.

**Your Public Content.** By submitting Your Public Content to Cheerful, including your public profile information such as your Display Name, you recognize that we store and may publicly display Your Public Content, along with your Display Name, in order to provide the Services that we offer.

**Feedback.** If you contact us to provide feedback, register a complaint, or ask a question, we will record any Personal Information and other content that you provide in your communication so that we can effectively respond to your inquiries.

**Activity.** We record information relating to your use of the Cheerful Services to administer the Cheerful Services and provide the highest possible level of service to you. Information such as searches performed, the pages viewed, your browser type, IP address, requested URL, referring URL, and timestamp information. We also use this information in the aggregate to perform statistical analyses of user behavior and characteristics in order to measure interest in and use of the various areas of the Cheerful Service. You cannot be identified from this aggregate information.

**Login location.** When you sign into Cheerful, we use your approximate physical location (based on the Internet Protocol address of your computer or your Current Location, should you choose to provide it, via your mobile device) to provide more relevant suggestions to you for places and other areas of the app that make use of location technology.

**Cookies.** We send cookies to your computer in order to uniquely identify your browser and improve the quality of our service. The term "cookies" refers to small pieces of information that a Website sends to your computer's hard drive while you are viewing the Services. We may use both session cookies (which expire once you close your browser) and persistent cookies (which stay on your computer until you delete them). Persistent cookies can be removed by following your browser help file directions. If you choose to disable cookies, some areas of the Cheerful Services may not work properly or at all.

**Enforcement.** We may use the information we collect in connection with your use of the Services (including your Personal Information) in order to investigate, enforce, and apply our TOS and Privacy Policy.

## Aggregated Statistics

Cheerful may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its Website and Services. Cheerful may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Cheerful does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

## Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

Cheerful discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Cheerful’s behalf or to provide services available at Cheerful’s Website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Cheerful’s Website and Services, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Cheerful will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Cheerful discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Cheerful believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Cheerful, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of a Cheerful Website and have supplied your email address, Cheerful may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Cheerful and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Cheerful takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

## Ads

Ads appearing on our Website or Services may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Cheerful and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

## Links to Other Websites

As part of the Services, we may provide links to or compatibility with other websites or applications. However, we are not responsible for the privacy practices employed by those websites or the information or content they contain. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by us through the Website and the Services. Therefore, this Privacy Policy does not apply to your use of a third party website accessed by selecting a link on our Site or via our Services. To the extent that you access or use the Services or the Cheerful App through or on another website or application, then the privacy policy of that other website or application will apply to your access or use of that site or application. We encourage our users to read the privacy statements of other websites before proceeding to use them.

## Integrating Third Party Services

Any Cheerful Services may offer the ability to share content created with a Service to online third party services, such as social networking services ("Third Party Services"). Any of the Services may ask you to provide your username and password for the relevant Third Party Services. By providing this information you are allowing the Service to pass your log-in information to a service to share content created with an Application. When you enable a Third Party Service account in a Service, it will collect your login information and other relevant information necessary to enable any of the Services to access that Third Party Service and your data contained within that Third Party Service. Please remember that the manner in which Third Party Services use, store, and disclose your information is governed solely by the policies of such third parties, and Cheerful shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any Third Party Service that may be enabled within an Application.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Cheerful may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Cheerful’s sole discretion. Cheerful encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns regarding privacy, please contact us at [help@chee.rs](mailto:help@chee.rs "Help"). Your privacy is important to us and we will make every effort to resolve your concerns.
